<resources>
    <string name="app_name">memory1</string>
    <string name="EnterGame">Enter Game</string>
    <string name="tap">Tap in game</string>
    <string name="action_settings6">Toggle PRACTICE MODE</string>

    <string name="action_settings5">Info + How to Play</string>
    <string name="action_settings4">Reset Statistics</string>
    <string name="action_settings3">Game Statistics </string>
    <string name="action_settings2">Game Settings</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Reset Score</string>
    <string name="PMon">Practice Mode ON</string>
    <string name="PMoff">Practice Mode OFF</string>
    <string name="PerfectSpeedy">Perfect and Speedy</string>
    <string name="ResetStats">Reset Statistics</string>
    <string name="PerfectRounds">Perfect Rounds</string>
    <string name="CInvisible">Calendar Invisible</string>
    <string name="CVisible">Calendar Visible</string>
    <string name="GoAgain">GO Again!</string>
    <string name="TapForStats">Tap for Game Statistics</string>
    <string name="SixImages">6 Images - Easy (default)  </string>
    <string name="NineImages">9 Images - Harder</string>
    <string name="MostRecent">Most Recent</string>
    <string name="Second">2nd</string>
    <string name="Third">3rd</string>
    <string name="Fourth">4th</string>
    <string name="GameScore">Game Score</string>
    <string name="ActualTimePlayed">Actual Time Played</string>
    <string name="PressesthisGame">Presses per Game</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="GameTitle">Welcome to Memory1 \n MainTrain Brain llc</string>
    <string name="Strategy1">Use your best VISUAL and AUDITORY CONCENTRATION to follow and tap
        the images as they appear. \n\n
        You can start tapping images as soon as they appear.
        But be careful! As you tap images their corresponding tones will play and can intermingle
        with the previewing image tones. \n\n
        <i>SCORING:</i> Correct taps play the corresponding unique tone for that image and score 25 points.\n\n
        Tapping a wrong/out of sequence image produces a low-pitch error tone and a score deduction of 25
        points.\n\n Whenever you make a wrong tap, or you are unsure of which image to tap next,
        KEEP GOING with your best memory or guesses. \n\n
        See GAME SETTINGS below for more info on scoring.\n
    </string>
    <string name="Strategy2">
        <i>GAME SETTINGS:</i>
        <b>Normal Preview</b> means each of the 6 images and tones are previewed 1 every .5 (one half)
        second, so that in Normal Preview the 6 images are displayed in 3 seconds. \n\n

        Playing with Normal Preview you will score a Speedy 100 point bonus for a Round played
        perfectly (6 of 6 correct taps) in under 5 seconds.\n\n

        <i>GAME SETTINGS:</i>
        <b>Faster Preview</b> is more difficult and means images and tones are previewed 1 every .25
        (one quarter) second, so that in Faster Preview the 6 images are displayed in 1 and one-half seconds.
        \n\n
        Playing with Faster Preview you will score a Speedy 100 point bonus for a Round played
        perfectly (6 of 6 correct taps) in under 3.5 seconds.\n\n

        For best accurate and meaningful game statistics you should only change the Image Preview speeds between
        full games - not between rounds. \n\n

        <i>ADVANCED AUDITORY ONLY:</i>
        As you get accustomed to the tones and become an advanced player
        you can try AUDITORY ONLY by holding a hand over your phone\'s display, or closing your eyes,
        while the preview is displaying - and concentrating on the tones played.
        \n\n
        Tap the tones back in the order you HEAR them.
       \n\n
        <i>ADVANCED VISUAL ONLY:</i>
        As you get accustomed to the visual hints and become an advanced player you can try VISUAL ONLY by
        muting your phone\'s audio so you only see the images previewed. \n\n
        Tap the images in the order you SEE them appear. \n\n
        <i>PRACTICE MODE:</i>
        Allows you to get used to the game and is easy and still fun to play. Practice Mode
        displays the images in left to right and down order. You can turn Practice Mode on and off
        by selecting Toggle PRACTICE MODE in the upper right dropdown menu.
      \n\n
        <i>Good luck. MainTRain your brain!</i></string>
    <string name="GameObject">The object of Memory1 is to tap the images in the same sequence they appear
        and their corresponding unique tones play,
        \n  "               "   <i>AS FAST AS YOU CAN</i>.</string>
    <string name="correctPresses">Correct Presses =  + 25 points</string>
    <string name="incorrectPresses">Incorrect Presses =  - 25 points</string>
    <string name="bonusForSpeedAccuracy">6 of 6 Correct Presses in under 6 seconds = + 100 Bonus points</string>
    <string name="pressScoring">Correct Presses  = + 25 Points \nWrong Presses =  - 25 Points \nSpeed Bonus  =  + 100 Points (6 of 6 within 2 seconds after final image is previewed)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_how_to_play">HowToPlay</string>
    <string name="enter_game">Enter Game</string>
    <string name="previewspeed">Image Preview Speed...</string>
    <string name="numberofimages">Number of Images... (to press in a round)</string>
    <string name="gameSettings">Game Settings</string>
    <string name="normalPreview">Normal Preview - Easy (default)"</string>
    <string name="fasterPreview">Faster Preview - More Difficult</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game_stats">Game Statistics</string>

</resources>

